I had given him my credit card to
use on his trip and then I
called the hotels where he had used it and asked whether the
same girl was there in every hotel or different ones,
well I mean he was loyal,
what is she
whistling with any one lady, I did not see that good boy, right?
[Sangeet]
When this happened, my father went to my neck
[Sangeet] and
I got a tongue to the sting,
oh friend, the
parrot's beak is broken, the parrot's beak is broken, you do
good work
[Sangeet]
yes you get money for that too, well
where else can you clean it
[Sangeet]
okay?  So we have kept this show
because as Sagar told, we used to do a lot of
shows.  So we have given this platform to
all the women to
say whatever they want.  I will not judge at all.
I am on your team.  Ok
?
My best past time is bitching men.
Everyone else is comfortable to talk to.
I have brought money for those who did not raise their hands.  Well, it's okay.
[cheering]
Okay?  So, the better the answers you
give, the more money I will keep giving you.
Ok?  This is a good fare.  Well, right now some
people are thinking that we should talk.
Ok?  So any story you have
, anything you want to tell, you
tell your best friend.
You guys can tell me that.  Correct.  Ok.   Let's
start well brother.  Give him the
mike.
Hi.  Hi.
Hi.
Hey, do you talk like this?  No.
Ok, good.  It's back to normal now.  Ok.
What is your name?
Rena.
Yes.
Or
what does it mean?
My Akshay name is Rena.  But are
you Renish or Indian?
Or [laughs] is that
such a big name for you?
Or
what does your name mean?   Don't know.
[laughter]
Never Googled Woogle?
Good.  So what did we tell you?  stay.
Ok.  If this conversation remains, it will go everywhere like YouTube,
Instagram, you have my consent for
this.  That is good.
So, have you come here to become famous?
[laughter]
No.
Tell the truth.   No. No.   Is
your account public or private?
Public.
Hey I am a musician.
These people have seen Siddhi Didi's video.
So, do you sing music?
Or
okay, you go home and sing.  Okay here.
[laughter]
Okay.
We have become the master of singing.  Good.
What do you do in life?  Meaning she sings full time
?
Or I'm a full-time musician.
And what do you mean, what type of songs do
you sing?  I mostly sing such pop music in English.
Well, where else do you sing?
I am based in Dubai.  So there's like
these restaurants and right now there's
no business, I mean.
Yes, right now it is a bit off like this.
Okay, okay.  And what do these tattoos mean
?  The tattoo on your hand, pass the mic a
little with your mouth.
This one?
Yes, that's what I see.  [laughter]
What a poor idea you guys have.
How do I know how many tattoos you had?
[sound of clearing throat]
about app
oh
one two three four five six brother this
looks like a boomer to me friend [laughs]
okay what does it mean what is this yes
explain this is
a skull and around it there is a snake and
flowers
so it it shows life and death
why did you make all this [laughs] by the way you don't know black
magic
you made it like this and that on the hand and
why are you wearing so many rings?
She is also wearing a snake ring.  And what
is that together with what?
There is a sun and there is a sunflower.
Well, there is sun, there is sunflower and there is something
written below, what is that?
That's a song lyric.
What is he reading?
You don't have to be sorry for doing it on
your own.
Which song is this?  [laughs] No
one should write like this.  The bug is the rickshaw driver.
Next, next for sure.   She
will write the next one.
Very nice.  In this, all that skull wall will go away.
[laughter] There was more.
What is that underneath it?
What is this here?  Not this, just a minute.  What is this?
I was discharged from the hospital yesterday.  That's
Ivy's this.
Well, you were in the hospital yesterday.
What happened to you?
Typhoid.
What makes you so happy?  [laughter] I'm typhoid.
Fancy yes.  poor u.  You will continue to have
piles.  [laughs]
I'm from Dubai, right?  Well, which
hospital were you in?  A hi,
what's okay?  Why is the girl next door asking?   I don't remember the
entire hospital in Lokhandwala.
So you go into anyone.  Hey doctor, I am here.
Apply saline under the tattoo.
[laughter]
You don't even know the name of the hospital.
I was not well.  Yes.   If
you were not well, did your mind go blank
?  [laughter] Was the typhoid so severe,
sir?  Okay, okay.  Yes,
what happened?  How major was yours like this?
Yes, I mean, like I was vomiting since 10
days, then it came again, it was
definitely typhoid
or [laughs] I am
asking, friend, I used to get dengue, that's why it was happening,
your thinking will go in that direction only, okay,
yes, what is
lady special,
ladies special, right? Yes, what should I ask
next [laughs]
yes, you have a boyfriend, what is his name? I am actually married,
but I am going to get divorced,
oh
why?
Friends, one seat is becoming vacant.  [laughs]
Because he's cheating on me.
What a joke?
And he doesn't know that I know.   We will know soon.
I am planning everything.
Well, here is the soft launch.  This is
soft.  What do you say?  Soft crashing.
Well, he doesn't know.
No.
And he was cheating in Dubai?
Yes.  Yes, he
is an international player [laughs]
how did you know that he is cheating,
I gave him my credit card to
use on his trip, so
he used it and then I
called the hotels where he used it and
asked who all had checked in, whether
my card was used, then they
gave me their IDs,
oh man it is sad, otherwise it was very sad
but now it is funny
because I am planning with my dad to kick him up
perfect
[cheering voice][applause]
and where did he go with your credit card, I
mean which country was he in?   I think he was
in Darjeeling.  Remember here, I was
in India,
yes in India
and you were in Dubai.
Yes.
So why did you give him the card?
I gave it to him as if he
needed it for extra expenses, so he could take it.
So he did it.
[laughs]
But I also felt bad that he did it with your money.   Or.
[laughter]
And was it the same girl at each hotel or
different?
Beans.  Well, I mean he was loyal.
Not with me, right?
With some woman.  But you are happy now
but in life?
Kind of.
Ok, good.  Meaning,
you just found out that I am over.
Yes, just like two weeks ago.
Can we do something to make you happy?
[laughter]
Hey, what
kind of nasty women are you guys?  A
man is asking a woman from his heart.   Give me some
liquor.   Do
you want to drink alcohol?
No.   Do
you drink alcohol?  Otherwise what can
I do?  I will give you some gift.
Ok?  Wait.  We have a gift by the way.
Where is this gift?  Yes, this is fine.
Yes, these caps are good?  This
is a cap from Urban Monkey.  Ok?  This is totally
cute.  [cheering voice] [applause] Do
you like it?
I love cats.
Oh!  So did you like Cat and Cap too?
Or it's so cute.  Thank you.
Or I gave it to you because
someone was making you wear the hat anyway.
[Applause]
How did you like my joke?  Everyone please clap once
for this.  [Applause]
Great.  Who else is there and who needs to talk?
Yes, brother, give him the mike.  Okay
okay ma'am, give him the mike.
Hello hi.
Hi.
What is your name?
Kaveri.
So Kaveri, all these things will
go everywhere like YouTube, Instagram.  I have your consent.
And do you have any brother or sister Kaveri?
What?   Do
you have any brothers or sisters?
My sister.   Is
she your real sister?
Good.  what is its name?
lights.
Ok.  Did the parents have to
make electricity?  [laughter]
That the light and the river got mixed up.
We are four sisters.
Oh!
Megha, Roshni, Kaveri, Janvi.
It looks like Bashpi Bhavan is happening.
[laughter]
And those two didn't come, the rest?
No.
What number are you on?
Third.
Good.  And this?
Seconds.
And there is a fourth one too.
Yes.  What did your family want when you were about to be born
?
Boy
Oh so you feel bad like this?
No [laughs]
why would it?
It is not my fault.
No, hey [laughs]
he played the victim card.
What is my fault?  This society which always
wants the lamp of the lineage.  [laughs]
Kaveri happened at their house.  No, it's okay,
friend.
When this happened, my father fell into the gutter.
[laughter]
No
[cheering voice]
No, she's lying.   Is
she lying?   She is
lying.
She's big, isn't she?
No.   She
is elder, she knows everything.
No, she is lying.  Which happened after me,
Janvi.   I
fell then.
Then there were the falls [laughter].  Is it Papa's hobby to do
gutter building,
Doctor Sahib, what happened to you girl, where
is the gutter [laughs] no no,
what happened,
and what about you brother, are you putting your own vine juice, what should I
say, some good child, nothing like that had happened,
he was happy, she is saying no, the time of the younger one, no no,
it is true that he fell in the gutter
[laughs] but
I understood why he wanted a boy as a child,
these girls are going out and
spreading all this [laughs]
no, when I was born, I mean, I had more
expectations that it would be a boy,
but it was not a boy, but during my time, we did
not fall in the gutter [laughs] but he was happy,
happy, do
you think I am a judge, does it depend,
Judge sir,
I am not that person
because she is lying, oh yes, it is
right, she is your sister,
then when the fourth time also a girl was born, then
Papa got very tensed,
then only then, but do
you people have some such royal
nickname that why did they
want a boy to continue that legacy, I don't know,
you never asked,
yes, what, what, you tell me  As for her,
she is saying tell them where we came from,
Solapur
or
guess the
gutter [laughs]
sorry sorry, not
Amarnath, not
Bangladesh,
not Darjeeling.
Now we will keep playing KBC.
1 minute 1 minute.  I decide after looking at your face.
Ok?
Nashik
Kurla.
How will those people come from Pakistan?   Will a
boy be named Kaveri in Pakistan
?
Never Nashik.
Nashik.
From Nashik.  And what did you get by doing this now?
[laughter]
You got to see it, right?
What did you get to see?
We will see you.  We have been sitting here since 3:00 pm from Nashik.
Oh man, thank you.  Thanks a lot.  [Applause]
Thank you.
And she has left her 9-month old daughter with her
husband.  You take care of it, I will watch the show.
Thank you friend.  Thanks a lot.
Meaning I should have come much earlier.  Much
more should have come earlier.  Meaning it's been a long time.
[laughter]
I'll come in advance.
Yes, but
thank you friend.  Look,
only girls can do all these things.  That's why I think girls are the
best.  Ok?  Girls who say yes
my father fell into the gutter.  What happened, what
happened?  Used to drink alcohol.  Best best friend, right right.  Give
a round of applause for these two.
[Applause]
Thanks a lot you both came.
And what my mother was telling me was that when
both of you reach Mumbai.
Yes.
So she would tell me on the phone in the morning that if
someone gave me something to eat there, then don't eat it.
[laughter]
Get a french fry.   Is
someone eating something for you?  Someone must be eating it.
Who is eating?  Yes, give two in front.  Who
is eating?  Aunties, give me your hands.  [laughs]
My mom told me not to.
Please, please, please
[encouraging voice] please
take it a little further.  Take it further.  Take it further.  [laughs]
My mom said no to it.
Hey you, you give it to me.
Hey, why are you crying? You have to
eat at least something, will
you feed me? [laughter]
[encouraging voice]
You can at least do this much, I will come for you
from Nashik.
[encouraging voice]
I have come today, mother, one should never
disrespect mother,
this is a lesson.  Never trust boys.
How did I kill the girl of the moment?   I didn't do it.   Didn't you do it
?  Were you going to eat it like that?
No.
Yes, it was seen.
Okay, when you eat, yes,
mother told me not to eat food from anyone else's hand.
Look, if it were mine, I would have fed it.  What did those aunties
bring?
Sir, really.
Really?  [laughter] It was
up to you.   Cute cute.
So give a round of applause
for these two.  [Applause]
What do you think of that person sitting in the corner
?  We should give money to this Kaveri.
How much should I give?  Whatever feels right to you,
yes?  Where is this?  Yes.
Whatever feels right to
me.  I am selling sarees
here.  [laughter]
Yeah, tell me.
should give.  Ok.
These
[praises]
and what else give it something else.  Yes,
you can keep this hoodie also.  You came from so far away for
me.  Thanks a lot.  Ok.  Please give this also.
Excellent.
Yes, now everyone will say that we have also come from far away.
Ok.  Who else is there?  And who
needs to talk?  Yes, okay.  Yes yes give it to him, give it to him.
Hi, what's your name?  Ok, good.
Yes yes yes, so Mansi, all these things will
go everywhere, YouTube, Instagram.  I have your
consent.  And what have you brought with
you?   For
you.
Brought it for me.  Oh thanks.  What is it friend?
See, today I had a lot of fun brother.  That's why girls are the
best, brother.  [laughter]
Girls, people don't bring anything.  What is?
Yes, till then tell me what do you do
in life Mansi?   Nothing.
So whose money is this?   It's worth
my money.
This is your credit card and some other [laughs]
oh brother.  I feel bad now.  I
spent this money using my father's money.  Whose
money did you use to do this?   With
my money.
This is the frame.  Oh wow.   It
's very nice, friend.  Yes, I will show you this.   I will show you.
What should we do with this garbage?  Yes, okay.  I
put it in my pocket.  No [laughter]
Yeah, okay.
Who likes it?   It's
very nice Ray.  What?
Oh well you have to see it too.  [laughter] It's
me and these are my parents.
This is mine, right?  [laughter] Are
you guys making fun of everything,
man.  Yes, take this.  Yes.   The
company is giving.
Who is he giving company to?  Yes, take this also.
Nice.
A note was also written in this bag.
Well, there is a note in it also.  Oh, he'll have that
tag.   It is
written on that tag.  Ok, good.
To the person who is the reason of my countless
laughter.  A little token of love from
me but you deserve the world.   I was
not supposed to read in front of everyone.
Good.
Who speaks after reading this?  [laughs] You should have
told me all this earlier and what is this that is written
?  98204
No, I will not tell you the whole story because write,
why are you laughing?  It was not written at all.  Okay
okay.  What were the names of Mansi?
Mansi.
What does Mansi do in life?
Why not?   I mean, I'm
not doing anything right now.
Okay, how old are you?
Here I was working.
Don't Mike Yes Stationery.  Earlier I was working with.
So, are you an air hostess?
Was.
Oh, I am not sitting right now.
No I just got trained as an air hostess but
I did not work.
So are you looking for a job right now?
Yes.
What type of job do you want?
Anything but my mother is
forcing me to do a government job.
So will you prepare for the government now
?
Good.  Are you happy in your life?
No.
[laughs]
You have a boyfriend.
Yes.
So why are you saying everything in such a sad manner
?  Boyfriend, yes.  [laughter]
Where is he?
He is at his home right now.
[laughter]
Traveling around Darjeeling.  Have you
come there to create trouble?  [laughter]
Yes.  So where did you find this boyfriend?
We Were Neighbors.  We lived upstairs
from the first floor.  [laughter]
What is all this?  Yes.  Top floor, bottom
floor?  [laughter] It was like that,
right?  What does the boyfriend do?   He is
a cinematographer.
Good.  And how many years have you been dating?   It's been
two-three years now.  [laughter]
Why, who's the one with the arm?  Are you seeing some scene going on
?
Best friend best friend.
Yes, so some scene is going on, you guys mean it is
going on right?
Yes, it is going well.  It just keeps going on and off.
Yes, that's why we want to know.  [laughs] Does that
mean he works in Bollywood?   No. No.
So what do cinematographers do?
Agents like wedding shoots, prewedding
etc.
Okay, okay, I understand.  Yes.  So
why does it turn on and off?
Why did you guys have your last time off?  It happened just the day before yesterday because
he is not giving me time
because I have shifted.
Because he has work.  [laughter]
He doesn't have it.   Sorry sorry.
I went to the wrong team, man.
Okay, yes, should I give time?
Yes.  Why does time tell you
how much time do you usually need?
How many times did you meet in a week?
At least you can text me before going to sleep at night, right
?
He doesn't even text.
No, he just says I am sleeping.  Good
night.  Bye.
So where does he say this?
But what kind of text is this?  I mean,
I stay put.   So
you wait the whole day thinking that
we will chat or talk at night.  But he comes and
says I am sleeping.
Yes.
Can we see the chat?
I am doing it for you.  [laughs] A
little bit please, I don't know, I don't know, there's nothing there.
Yes, everything is fine.  Anyway, you wo
n't have any romance left right now.  That's why boys fall asleep as soon as the conversation begins.  Is
this sorry sorry
I [laughs]
ok boys do wrong, you should
give more time to others [laughs] you should keep pampering them, there is nothing, what have
you done, yes I unlocked it, yes okay okay,
yes what is this chat,
which app is this, this is a
chat.
Oh so this is showing [laughs]
oh everything disappears on this, for something to
disappear there should be something, there is nothing,
okay this is it, I could sleep, no, I could not sleep,
oh sorry sorry yes I [laughs] it is a
sentimental message, friend, this is, I could not sleep, sorry, sorry, I was
saying, oh what is this
[laughs] what do my, my eyes are moist, right now,
stop for 2 minutes in between the emotional message,
don't go to the washroom, my
eyes are moist, but I have also come to cover them.  [laughter]
Oh brother, no, you guys laugh, you guys laugh,
what do you have to do, brother, are
you sad or happy? You've become so lazy, you
just want to see content [laughter] Oh, my God,
people chat so much on Snapchat,
oh brother, what can
we do about it, okay, you had a
dream in life, you wanted to
become an IAS officer, you became one, right? You
can't go now, can you join now? You started training,
but I just lost my
mind, will I have to
train again for three months, then all
the exams and all? Who will do it so
well?
This is called efforts,
I made them too,
okay [sound of clearing throat]
but it wasn't in my destiny, so it wasn't meant to be,
so okay, okay, have you
ever fallen in
love,
yes,
when
[laughter]
what a cheap guy you are, hey, right now, yes,
clap for this, everybody
[applause]
Whom do you ask, yes, this girl in Specs,
yes, what do you think we should pay her,
how much [nasal sound]
why a thousand,
say on or off?  [laughs]
Okay, right, let's give it to him. Okay, yes,
take this and give it to him.
Thank you,
great. [applause]
You had to do this. Stop it. You have to do it. Give it to him.
Mike Kavya. This whole conversation will
go everywhere, YouTube, Instagram. This is your
consent.
Of course, the work is the same.
Kavya, what do you do?
Ah, I am a chemical engineer, an actor and
also a content creator.
What does it mean, brother, you are not able to do one thing properly?
Why did you do engineering by the way
?   For
me too, it is still in question mark.
Because I did it because my
family told me to do it or I had to do it.
And there are
very few girls in chemical engineering, right?
Yes.
How many boys were there?  [laughs] I
think girls 9-10
and boys
so for one boy no no this is
it [laughs]
no I am asking according to the ratio
yes one what who is doing
this when did you decide that content first you
entered into content creation and what is the third
thing what was
acting
well you are doing acting also
yes so
what did you start first
first chemical engineering then content
creation and now like struggling actor
and what type of content do you make?
Fashion, Beauty, Lifestyle, Everything.
Well, he just gets ready with time.
Hey, what about normal times, all of you
people are judgmental bastards.  You are judging everything.
And why do you want to learn acting?
Meaning, do you want to become an actor or do theatre
?   Have to
become.  I want to become an actor.
Good.  And who is your favorite actor?
Ramcharan?
Yes.  Who is asking?  Who is he?  Do
n't you guys know Ramcharan?  Well, that was in RRR.   She
watches Pakistani dramas.  Right, right, okay.
Let's talk.  Okay, yes, okay.
Ok.  So what do they teach in acting workshops
?  Meaning, how do you teach
?  I have thought and heard that they have many such
viewer tricks.
Or is that the
touching one you guys have?
Which touching?
Ok.  I used a very wrong word [laughs].  There is
something like this, right?  What did you guys say
?
Meaning, whatever your partner is, whatever is
good for you, make him comfortable with him.
This happens
or it
was torn [laughs]
he is not comfortable like that, yes tell me
what should I do, acting touching
but like eye contacts and everything,
meaning
you just look at the person for 2 minutes
and how will you become comfortable acting with this, let's do it,
you and I will do it, okay
I am doing it for work, okay
[laughs]
look, it has become 44 now.
what is your name?
Purvai
Purvai, you become a volunteer.  Ok.  Yes.
[laughter]
Oh, the east wind, do
n't wait an hour.
[laughter]
Why should I blink?  Yes, this is
not a competition at all.  [laughter]
East Wind
Yeah, okay, that's it.   Am
I an actor now?  [laughs]
Now I'm an actor.  Do
you want to see my acting?
[laughter]
70 million.
Wow, I came inside.  [laughter]
Well what happens with that
anyway?
You basically become comfortable with the industry.
So do you make those who are doing romantic roles do it
or do you make everyone do it?
Everyone.
Well, after that did
you guys reach acting?  I mean, even the dialogues?
Yes.  We place it.
What do you do?
Place.
Well, I mean, you do that role play.
Good.
Hey, that's what we call him.
Two days ago, I was a mother of three children.
[laughs]
Otherwise, you guys do some such speech therapy as
well, I mean
you guys are not clear, I mean it also happens
that dialogues have to be spoken clearly, if there is something like this then let
me give you a tongue
twister, hey
friend, it will be fun, I am
trying
parrot's beak broken, broken beak parrot, you have to
speak this fast, okay, hey
parrot's beak broken, broken beak
parrot, hold the mic close, friend,
I am definitely going to poop,
hey [laughs] If not to poop, then she also went on
Snapchat,
yes, hey, it will be fun only if no one poops.
Okay, yes, just [laughs] of course, I
mean, we need
content, yes,
broken [laughs] the
parrot's beak is broken, the parrot's beak is broken, the parrot's beak is broken, the parrot's beak is broken, the parrot's beak is broken, right
now we are doing it fast, okay
Mike, a little fast, the
parrot's
yes, yes [laughs] the parrot's beak is
broken, the parrot's beak is broken, the parrot's
[laughs]
why are you hitting the parrot brother?
Made a female parrot.  No no who will
concentrate now it will be fun [laughs].  Yes oh
my god okay.  The parrot's beak is broken, the
parrot's beak is broken [laughs].   The
parrot's beak broke.
I am not even repeating it.  Now [laughter]
you understand how well I did.
Yes and this last one last yes these are your
friends, right all of them are
actors these people are
not
you yes so after this you will do this [laughter]
and you like this you travel a lot by local train
so why have you kept your bag
in your lap [laughter]
aunty you are sitting like this aunty where will you get off
I have to go to Kalyan [laughter] okay yes yes
last one and one more time yes
parrot's [ __ ] [
laughter]
broken beak parrot just
say parrot
yes Pur Bhai Pur Bhai where are you from by the way
Ahmedabad
okay so you are very rich oh
shut up [laughter]
no
you are so rich
so how come you have such an accent I mean
I speak like this
okay you have studied from ICSE school
no I mean
you have studied till like
10th grade [laughter]
yes okay okay and you are also becoming an actor
you were also a content creator come on
[laughter] sorry sorry
yes continue
and model too
oh brother brother you are very tall
how tall are you
if you can stand
[nose
[voice of clearing throat] Oh brother,
friends, applause for Khali [laughter]
we are saying something for you, will you
come on stage or not,
okay, you don't want to be famous, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay,
first sit down, then we will try, sit down, sit down,
okay, comfortable, hey, what is
your height, by the way,
59, so it happens like this that
you mean short boys, have you
ever hated you,
yes [sound of clearing throat]
so what do you say,
refuse, come on,
Chotu, get out like this [laughter]
what is your criteria, six
[sound of clearing throat]
so even if someone comes, six one,
what is it for me [laughter] I am only 62, like this
[encouraging voice] hey, okay, I mean, it is
everywhere.
What is this everywhere?  And what have I done here
?  [laughter] Or I'll see women everywhere.   Okay
okay.  Yes.  So what do you say,
if we assume there is a very good looking
boy, his personality is also good but he is only
6 feet tall.  So if he approaches you.  Is there
anyone in your life right now?
No.
Well, let's say someone approaches
you.  So
how many 62 is your shortest boyfriend hiding
?  Six
I've only had one boyfriend.
Yes, okay.  What was his height?
51.   So, do
you have any such trauma?
[laughter]
So how did he teach you?  His game was good.
Is the one minute game good?  Hey, one minute.
What does the game mean?  This [laughs]
game was good, I mean it's a game to talk about.
What does this game mean?
[laughter] Wrong, brother, should call the boys.   No no, I
mean you understood what I was
saying.  Yes,
we have not done anything.
Oh no what?  [screaming voice] Am
I the only bad guy I'll ever look like on the
internet?  Didn't we do anything?  What?
Hey game means 1 minute.  If someone is a smooth talker
then his game is good.  This is what I am saying.   I
mean it was okay.  [laughter]
What can I say after this?  Ok.  Ok.
So let's do one thing.  If you
are comfortable then I will become a short boy.
And I will talk to you.  Ok?
And then we will see.  Anyway, you guys are
learning acting, right?  Ok?  So let us
try.  Ok?  Yes.  It will look better if you come on stage
because then you will
not be able to judge the height from so far away.  Yes.  Hey what?
You guys have such small thinking.  Yes, come, come.
Yes.  What?  [laughs]
We've now banned men for all these things.  She is whistling.  [laughs] I didn't
see a good boy, did I?
Ok.  Ok.  Did the girl hit [laughs]
Okay.  Ok.  Yes, okay.  So I'm short, right
?  Yes.
[laughter]
No, come up a little.  This much
is fine.  Sit down.  [laughter]
Oh, I'll be less likely to sit down.
Yes, okay.  I live this much.  Ok.
Where are we?  Some [laughs] oh some
location should be decided.
What was yours on the beach?
That's why no one talks to you.  [laughter] The
beach is still okay, right?   For
one thing, my game is very bad.
[laughter]
Now we're strangers.  What should I talk about now
?
[laughter]
Hello.  exuse me.   Yes.
[laughter] Are
you from around here?  What?  Are you from Mumbai
?
No.
Well actually
I had to book a cab.  My phone is dead.
Can you book a cab for me
please?   Don't
talk nonsense.  Ok.  [laughter]
Talk to two tall people.   There
is no space for bottles for a minute.  Ok.
Girls with I five two.
I also don't talk to you.
Yes,
okay, I will do it.
Oh please.  So actually I am new in this city so
I have no idea at all.  So
I actually had to go to Andheri.  Where do you
live by the way?
Darkness.
Oh [laughter] so
not if you're going too.
[laughter]
Okay.  Ok.  I actually I hope
I am not boding you.   What are you doing.
sit quietly.
Ok.  You book a cab.  I will go for that.
Yes, should I enter the location or
will you?
Two.
Yes.  No.  F I have.   Whether
I am new in town or not.  That [laughs]
my phone battery is dead.  So I will
book it from your phone.  So please.  Yes,
okay.   No no, there
is no need to give it literally.
Lou
[laughs]
Yeah, yeah, okay.  It's booked.
Delete it.
what?
No number.
What number?
What you just put in.
No, I have entered this location.  Friend,
why are you thinking like this?  [laughs] Just
look, I didn't put the location.  So if
you have linked your card in it then
probably the payment will be made.
And my father had said that one should not keep anyone's money.
And actually my wallet was also left at home.
So if [laughter]
no I don't have a Jeep.
Oh, so if you live in Andheri then I
can bring the cash also.
No.
Ok.  Ok.  No one, I am going.
Ok.
[laughs]
Girls friend [laughs]
Strong girls
[cheering voice]
This one will be cut, there will be a 51 year old boy [laughs]
No, great, okay, clap for this
once [applause]
Thank you brother, what is the end of this,
I don't have anything and yes, okay, it happens like this, oh my
god, Pur brother, what have you done to
me like this, Pur
how many followers do you have by the way?   Have
you ever received a DM from any such famous person 247?
Yes.
whose?
Cricketer.
Oh [laughs] that's a very common thing.  So
what did you say?
[Encouraging voice]
Hey, do that to everyone.  Once
he did it to me at 1:00 in the night.  [laughter] Brother, I
said, no brother.   I don't wanna say it.
A then we will beep.
If you are comfortable then there are
trust issues.
Okay, you have a trust issue, okay, you have to do
one thing, just spit on my face,
you have already rejected me [laughs].
I said
you won't do it by beeping.  I have trust issues.
Oh okay.  Ok.  Excellent.  Do one thing,
give the mic to Kavya.
Who is that meaning?  Oh well, yes.  Oh well, fine.
Yes.  Kavya, have you ever received DMs from any
famous person?
Yes, I have come.
Whose did it come for?  If you can tell me.
Not some such copy, normal DMs can also come.
Yes, I am
coming.
Like
Kamal R Khan.  I don't know hit name.
Good KRK.
Or or oh
no I am asking a famous person.  [laughter]
Oh traitor
₹2 person.  You got a message from him.
Who lost in this?  [laughs]
What message did you get from him?  Nothing
that hi you would be a big star one day remember
my words
yes to him tell him when will you be [laughs]
and someone else's is it
and or I think so
cricketers friend
ok cricketers only message everyone yes
oh
I trust you
yes but I don't remember the name [laughs]
okay your boyfriend is Ekvya
no, have
you ever had a bad breakup
yes there was one in school time
then what happened I ran away with your sandwich.
[laughs] Can
you guys expect me to abuse you, she
looks so cute.   It is about
ninth or tenth standard.
How did you woo me in ninth or tenth standard
?   She
came laughing like this.
[laughs]
Kavya, don't do all this.  Ok?  Not after the show.
Yes.  So why did
you guys break up?   It was
not working out like that.  End.
What wasn't working?  In ninth 10th standard.
I thought it was funny but it wasn't funny.   So
what are your requirements?
What three things do you look for in a man?
Must be caring.
Ok.   It
should be funny.
Nice.
And
[laughter]
yes, yes, you can also say it.  You also speak.   Is there a
Swayamvar going on here?  Everyone is
telling their own story in the middle.  Kavya and I should
talk, Kavya, you should talk about the same thing, it should be from
Navi Mumbai, it should be from
Navi Mumbai, oh my God it's
a match [laughs]
I live in Kargar, I know you, you want to do
some acting,
what do you want to do, should I tell you what acting is,
oh brother, this Purvai lives here, you have the attitude, I
understand, you will do something with me at the end,
okay, let's try, then, okay,
clap once for these two
[applause]
whom should I ask, yes, yes, let's ask him, how much should I
give,
500, thanks,
you have saved my money.   It is
given according to height.  So, they
loot a lot on Purvai, brother.  Excellent.  Who else is there?
Who wants to talk?  I am talking to you.
Ok.  So in between I went to
see a play.  I also posted a story
if you have seen it.  It was a Marathi play.
Thir Life For Ever was his name.  So, all the
writers and actors have
come today, so please clap for Akshata once.
Hi hi hi hi
how are you?   Okay,
and how is your theatre thing going
?
How's the run or yes going?   It's
going well, very well.
Right right.  So these stories that you have
written, how many times have they been
first played?
Well, you wrote this first.
First play ever or
great.  So there are some more such stories of your life
which you want to share.
Well uh like what?  You only tell me.
Yes.
What to share?  [laughs]
You have a boyfriend.
No, not yet.   So
how long have you been single now?   Its been
three years.   Have
you tried any dating apps?
No.
So, after a certain point,
your social circle becomes limited.
How do you meet new people then?   It's the
same theatre, but it's a small world.  You
go around and meet the same people.   There are only
three people in your play
anyway.  [laughter] The
one in there is single.
So how does that make you feel?   He
is nice.
And if he asks you out on a date, should I
give him the content?   Is this
your scene?
No.   Is this
Not there.
No, no, not yet.
Well, it means something, right?
No, not yet.  If it happens then I will
come and tell you in the next show.  Sure.
We need it in this video.  [laughter]
Where does he live?
On the lower.   It's
not long distance
but you can relate to it
because it's the
same pain in
Kharghar Panvel it's the same only
no,
okay
for us Mumbai is long distancing
yes yes what is this cut off [laughs] okay okay
I take the joke sportingly okay
and the option is also gone yes [laughs] have you
ever had such a nasty breakup, was the reason long
distance relationship but the first one
which was
long distance means where did he live
in Mumbai.  [laughter]
Where did he live?
So at first we were in the same school.
Yes.
And
his history is a bit boring.  I
mean, he doesn't have any
relationship history, I mean, we were in ninth grade
when we met for the first time, but I was told that
he was so sincere.  So she
said I love you.  I love you is done.  But then he
said that we will not date.  This is happening
in a school in Panvel.  yes [laughs]
or
he said quickly yes tell me my
train to Panvel is leaving no no so he said
we will wait a bit
let's be adults so to be official
we will wait
what a joke which school was this
or I will take the name
ok yes okay yes so but
and I was like yes let's go you are saying okay okay
he was a year older than me so I was like
yes let's go okay okay and
the first two years were great great I mean
what do you mean what will you do in school other then
I don't know [laughs] I still don't
know yes yes
okay but then
he went away to do engineering
osa
and I was here so the chemistry
remained only on the pages it never got translated and then he told
me that when your 12th gets over then
we will make some big gesture like this we
will officialize our relationship we will tell everyone
that we are in a relationship now.  So as
promised he came back but that relationship did
not become official and that day we broke up.
Why did he do this?  Yes, again, I was
not giving time.  So, she can relate, right
?
Meaning, it was like I love you.  What now?   It was
not official.  The rest was it or meaning.
I do not know.  [laughter] Okay.
What about the second one?
Second one I waited for like a year before
dating.  Then I Met This Guy.
Where did you meet me and you?
Theatre through itself.
Ok.  Yes.
So we clicked and after that we dated for seven years.
Yes.  Yes
and then he also went away Pandit,
what do you do like this?
I think people have a toxic trait
that I think their
visa gets approved quickly because of me.  So [laughs] I
think I want to go
out to Dubai?
So his visa is torn.
Oh, yes, okay, okay.
What is the most romantic thing you have done in love?
Romantic, did
someone say from behind,
ok visa,
yes, have
these girls gone mad [laughs],
yes,
I am also thinking, when have I ever done this, I have
not done this,
yes, okay,
a romantic gesture is, did I do a treasure hunt on her
birthday, after that I
gave her a little expensive gift,
tell me, expensive.
Marshall Speakers.
Well, are they expensive?
Yes, they are expensive.
Okay, okay, okay, no, I do
n't know.  We know the boat cost Rs 1,200.
[laughter] Blinkett comes home immediately.
So you gave Marshall gifts, and
do you give expensive gifts?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
,
no, that's it.  That's when Budget Two.   There is
a boy who is eating.
[laughter] I'll get the speaker then.
Clap once for Akshata.  Pass this.
Yes, great.  Yes, whom should I ask?
Yes, the one in green, what do you think,
you don't, green green, yes you only, you only, yes
what do you think, should we
give money to Akshata, she has
come from Panvel, we should
not give her money, are you joking, okay
friend,
two, two, there has been a breakup,
two, who said so,
500 500 two, 500 500 two, two
notes, just
two, no no
two, yes no no,
okay, don't fight, I will
not, two notes please,
two notes, no yes, okay, okay, I will give you two, okay, I
feel you, two, two, for the breakup, yes
yes [laughs] that's it.  Great applause
for this.  Yes, okay.  One last thing we can do.
Ek Kavya, do you want to do
any acting?  What did you
do with the three kids?
You are talking about the mother of three children, sister, she got
scared immediately.  Which three children are there?  Give it forward.  Pass the
mic forward.  Yes.  You
will tell her some plot which she will act.
What do you mean?  Not the one with three kids.  This is what
Houseself does.
No means I become a housewife.
[laughs]
Hey, an actor is an actor, brother.   A
good
actor should be ready for everything.
This is your test.  I will become the housewife
and you become that pervert.   I
mean, the one who was
her boyfriend.
Not good.  Has this become too intense
?  Do you have any other suggestions?
What to do?   It would be
nice. Have
n't you paid the house fees?  Do I have to
sweep here?  No no,
I will not do any work, I mean I will just
play a role, what do I have to suggest to anyone, this is
good, you want to make me a maid only, okay, okay
Kavya, you will come on stage, yes yes,
great,
hey, housemaid, I mean, does she just sweep, there are
other works too,
what else am I doing, wait for a minute, one minute,
tell me what all should we do, you have
just finished your work,
you decide which work.  [laughter]
I'm a housewife, right?  Yes.  I have
come to his house after doing some work.
She's coming home to her boyfriend right now.  You are
meeting at your boyfriend's house.
No, who is this?
Here, only when the boyfriend comes, there will be drama.
Otherwise what's the fun?
Yes.
[laughter]
Poorvai.
I am not afraid of slaps.  Looks like from the east.
Yes.  So who is Purvai?
1 minute.  Purva is the girlfriend.  Yes, so
you come a little late in the scene.  Ok?  Right now I am a
house self.  You are her boyfriend.
Yes.   Did you
understand everything?  Did everyone understand their work?
Ok.  Let us go.  Anyone have some Chunni
Wunni?
Yes, keep it with yourself.  [laughter]
Okay, okay.  Yes.
Hey, I'm cleaning it up.  I will do it with my hands only
now.  Hey, do you have your handkerchief?  No, is it someone
's handkerchief?
Yes, give it to me. Yes, give it to me. Yes,
clean it, don't make it dirty. Yes, it's okay.
[laughs] you do a
good job. Yes, you
get paid for it.
Where can a woman clean it? A
woman will do everything. I will do this too. Whatever
is dirty, [laughs] I will do
everything and go.   Are you
tired?   Yes
?   Are you
tired?
No, just a little.
Yes.
Will I take some rest?
Where will I rest?  Right now.   Sit down.   Take
rest.
Sure?
Yes.
No, not all this
[laughs] That's it, that's enough, that's enough, that's enough, no
problem,
yes, okay
[laughs]
Oh, they're just sitting there, aren't they?
[laughs] It feels
good at my house,
yes, I mean, it feels like this [laughs]
And how do I look?
[laughter]
Sir, what are you saying, sir?
Hey, I am asking how I feel?   I look
hot.
Okay [laughter]
So then the
point?
Hey, you are a man.
Taking my card [laughter]
[cheering voice]
[applause]
what should I tell you
[laughter] I went to Darjeeling?
You need my card.
Your card?
Credit [laughs] card.   Do
you have a credit card?  Do you have a credit
card? Yes, I take it with me when I go to DMart.
Ok.  [laughter]
So you're sad right now?
No, I feel fine.  It
feels good to share it with you.  Feeling light.
Well
[laughs]
you're sad so I can do something.   But I can do it.
Why are you saying this?  [laughter]
Yes?  So make some tea and bring it.
[Encouraging voice]
What can you do?  [laughter]
Tell me, what should I do to make you happy?
You are there, right?
Will you come a little closer?
[laughter]
Squeeze my feet.
What do I care?  Will you increase my salary?
I would like it.  Well, I am happy with that.
What else can you increase?
Good.  [laughs]
Okay, Nita ji, sorry about the dialogue.  [laughs]
I just wanted to be happy.  I would love to.
How many children do you have?
Three.
[laughter]
His role fell upon him.  There are three.
Good.   When
he comes after drinking, the children grow up.
No problem.   The
fourth one has to be done.  [laughter] Ca
n't talk about anything.
[laughs]
Then I wasn't ashamed to do three.   So it happens.
Good.   I
fell
[laughs]
when [laughs] she is making fun of
her own father, saying that she did
not feel ashamed when she had three children, but she felt ashamed when her husband
fell in the gutter [laughs]
but I like your girlfriend very much,
she is beautiful too, so
yes my choice is a bit different.
What is your choice?
You look good even though you are tired.  [laughter]
So what do you want?
I want a lot of things.
Like let's show it.
Hey girlfriend come.
Now should I lie down completely?
[laughter]
Come closer.
You will come, how will I come?  No, you will not come.  Yeah, so
then [laughs]
set the scene for tonight.
No, it should be done the opposite way.
[Encouraging voice] [Laughter] So
do it,
sir.   Do
work.  What are you doing?  Do work.  [laughter] He
wore this just to insult me.
Sir, why did this empty house come to your house?  [laughter]
Madam, please clean this fan.
[encouraging voice]
I'll clean these up a little.
[Sound of clearing throat]
I will rule this house.
Hey hey what is happening?
What is happening to us [laughter]?   Do
work.  What are you doing?
What is this happening?   Do
work.
[laughter]
Nothing's going on, baby.  Nothing, everything is fine.
[laughter] I
need some end.  [laughter]
You say something.  Abuse me.
Hey,
then you also give me a short back.  Ok.
[laughs] It's still actually
not my time.
Hey
[encouraging voice]
Look, I think we got a really good ending.
Okay, I mean, but
[laughs] it wouldn't be nice to end on a lady
special.
And the ending is happening, so
I think if you're a couple, then let's end on a kiss.
You both
clap once for them.
Rest thanks a lot.  Thanks for coming.  Jai
Hind Jai Maharashtra.  O!